- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
- Bite My Neck -
From here, the winger,
Mahan, will pass to Khan.
Then Tahel will cover from this position.
All right.
Okay! We'll run through this play
once Mahan and the others are back.
Let's get the championship title back.
We'll wipe the smirks off
those Decelis guys' faces.
Right, Captain?
Huh? Uh, sorry.
What'd you say?
We're discussing our game
plan for the nightball game.
Oh, right. Yeah, I agree.
Were you even listening?
O-Of course I was.
Then what did we say?
Basically, I just need to score, right?
Khan, something's off about you today.
You've been absent-minded all day.
Th-That's not true.
Did something happen?
N-No, nothing happened.
I'm just tired.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, by the way,
this is from them.
A dog?
They're looking for a fight.
Apparently, it's an invitation
to their birthday party.
What should we do?
We'd never go to that.
Who'd celebrate their birthday?
Right?
But you guys said you wanted to go.
We were just being polite.
Are you okay?
You should get some rest.
Yeah.
Goodnight.
It must be because of the total eclipse.
But why'd it have to be a human, huh?
Still, I hope it works out.
You sent them an invitation?
It's not like I had a choice.
Sooha said she wanted to invite them, too.
If that's what Sooha wants,
it's not like we can say no.
Still, I don't like celebrating
our birthday with werewolves.
What does Sooha even
like about them, anyway?
Don't ask me.
It's because they hate vampires, isn't it?
Yeah.
Don't remind me.
I'll never get over it.
Don't worry about it.
She didn't know about us
when she said that.
If Sooha finds out what we really are,
she'll never want to see us again.
It doesn't matter what she thinks.
This is why I said not
to get close to her.
What? But I want to be friends with Sooha!
I never expected her to
hate us that much, though.
Nobody likes us.
It's natural for a human to hate us.
And her friend was killed by vampires.
We don't hurt humans, though.
We know that about ourselves.
But to humans, we're no
different from other vampires.
Telling her we're an exception
won't solve the problem.
True. We can't force her to trust us.
It's not like anyone's ever
believed us before.
Then we have no choice.
We'll tell Sooha that Solon is a vampire
so the rest of us will be off the hook.
Huh?!
What?!
Solon's a vampire?!
That's right. It caught
us by surprise, too!
Let's not waste any time.
Here's some firewood.
Here's a light.
Die, you horrible vampire!
Solon, we won't forget your sacrifice.
We'll keep you in our hearts forever.
Hey!
Noa, why are you gathering firewood?
And Jino, why are you lighting it?
But I gathered so much.
I'm playing along.
You can't be serious!
Sheesh! Your sacrifice
would solve everything!
Then you sacrifice yourself!
That's enough. For now, you two will
be the candidates for that plan.
I'm not a candidate for anything!
In any case, let's make sure she
doesn't find out what we are.
Yeah.
We should avoid using our
powers as much as possible.
If she finds out what we are,
we won't be able to stay here anymore.
I thought we'd get to stay
at this school for a while.
I doubt Sooha would tell anyone even
if she found out we're vampires.
You don't know that.
Vampires don't feel any love at all.
Vampires are just cold, brutal monsters!
Werewolves are way better!
No, you can't even compare them.
Vampires are the worst!
Heli.
There you are.
Um, I'm sorry about earlier.
I got so worked up.
It's fine. I know how much
you hate vampires.
It's only natural.
Yeah. Thanks.
We forgot to give this to you earlier.
Come to think of it, you said
there was a birthday coming up.
Everyone would be glad to see you there.
I hope you'll come.
Of course! By the way,
whose birthday is it?
All of ours.
Huh?
None of us knows the day we were born.
Oh...
Then what's this day?
It's the day we left the orphanage.
After the hell we went through
the day we fled Vanfield,
you guys still trust humans?
Is anyone chasing us?
No, we're good.
There's a house!
You ran away from the orphanage?
We don't use this storage shed.
It's safe here, so you can rest.
Th-Thank you.
It's okay. I won't tell anyone.
This will help a lot.
Yeah.
Let's leave once we've had a little rest.
I'm hungry.
Me, too.
Suck it up.
You must be hungry.
These are just leftovers, but...
Vampires showed up?
We have to kill them all this instant.
So this is where you've been.
Didn't I tell you?
It's dangerous outside the orphanage.
Now, let's go back to Vanfield House.
We can only trust each other.
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
Sooha, you mentioned before that
your friend was killed by vampires.
Yeah.
Were you close?
You know how I have that weird power?
It made people think I was a vampire,
so I was always all alone.
My parents told me never to use my power.
Chris was the only one who understood me.
But one day...
Chris is still inside!
You can't go in there!
Let go of me!
Chris has a bad leg!
Hey, you!
All I could think about was saving him.
Don't do it, Sooha.
If anyone sees you,
they'll get the wrong idea.
Everyone will think you're a vampire.
Chris!
"I don't care what anyone thinks."
"I don't care what anyone says about me."
Chris!
Hold on!
I'll save... you...
In that moment, I thought...
I'd been given this power
so I could do this.
I believed...
that you'd come.
I may never find
another friend like Chris.
He even told me to bite his neck once
because he believed I wasn't a vampire.
Not even I could trust myself, but he...
I could never like vampires.
Sooha.
Want to try biting my neck?
Huh?
What?!
W-Wait, what are you talking about?!
I mean, it's not like
I hate you or anything...
I know.
We were kids back then.
The situation is totally different now.
We're on our way to
becoming adults, you know?
I-In any case, that's that!
So?
Go ahead.
No! This is too embarrassing!
I can't do it!
But I trust you that much, too.
Huh?
It's true.
Wh-What about you, Heli?
What?
Could you bite my neck?
Oh, uh...
See? You think it's embarrassing, too!
Well, so do I!
Y-You're right.
To be honest, one of the reasons I wanted
to come to this school was its library.
It has a lot of old books, so I thought
I could find the vampire's weakness.
But some vampires showed up
at the plaza the other day.
That was my first time
actually seeing one,
and I'd never been so terrified.
I couldn't stop shaking.
It was like my whole body froze.
But that made me realize something.
Vampires really are monsters.
I see.
I'd better head back.
Thanks for coming to deliver this.
Everyone's excited to see you there.
Okay.
Mahan, how are things over there?
We still don't know where our
missing friends were taken.
Apparently, someone saw
vampires near this town.
I see. We entered Decelis to
investigate that girl's death,
but those vampires didn't
have anything to do with it.
As if they'd ever tell you the truth.
It's a fact that vampires
are attacking our friends.
Yeah, but I saw them fighting
vampires the other day.
At the very least,
they didn't seem like allies.
Either way, several werewolves
have gone missing from town.
Vampires must be involved somehow.
They'll come after you, too,
if they learn you're vampires.
Be careful when you transform.
I know.
Ruslan, you'll be back in time
for the nightball game, right?
Of course.
Kamil, you're not out of shape, are you?
Don't worry about me.
We'll call again later.
Sure.
Bye.
Huh? Khan...
Khan might be bothered
that he can't transform.
I don't know about that.
None of us care about that.
We couldn't ask for
a better leader than Khan.
Yeah.
But everyone's bothered
by different things.
Are you part vampire?
I don't even know what I am.
I'm not the only one.
It's the same for the other guys.
Are the werewolves actually coming?
They haven't responded
to our invitation yet.
Then I bet they aren't.
Apparently, we're still preparing
things in case they show up.
What do you think of this?
You've always been a great artist.
I helped with this spot around here.
My masterpiece!
What's wrong?
Heli dropped the cake.
I'm really sorry.
It can't be helped.
We still have time. Let's make a new one.
You can't have a birthday
party without a cake.
We'd better go buy the ingredients.
Let's ask Jakah to do it.
What?!
What do you think? Pretty nice, right?
Jakah, sorry, but we need some
things bought in a hurry.
Sure thing. I've got this.
Huh? Is it burnt?
Thanks for waiting.
You saved the day.
It's convenient having Jakah
around at times like this.
There's no ramen.
What?
That wasn't on the list.
Heli, did you forget to write it down?
Do we even need ramen?
But...
I really want ramen...
I have to go out again?!
It's nearly time.
Hey, Sooha!
Welcome.
We've been waiting for you!
What a lovely place.
Thanks for coming.
I bet it was tough getting out here
to the middle of the woods.
No, it was fine. I was surprised, though.
I didn't expect to find a beautiful
mansion this deep in the woods.
Right? I built it.
Actually, we were just fortunate
enough to inherit it.
What? From who?
There was someone who supported
us after we left the orphanage.
Oh...
They did a lot for us, but they passed
away, so we inherited this place.
I see.
Since we live in the dorms, we only make
it out here on weekends and summer break.
The garden is beautiful, too.
I maintain it.
That's a lie, too.
Come in. I'll show you around.
Sooha.
Khan!
H-Hey.
Next time, Episode 6:
"Hunter's Moon: Birthday Party."
- Birthday Party -